Previously on Z Nation.
This is Citizen Z.
There is a man traveling among you.
His name is Murphy.
Your name wouldn't happen to be Murphy,
would it?
His blood has the antibodies
to create a vaccine.
The Centers for Disease Control
is offering an enormous bounty
for Murphy's safe delivery.
Keep alive at all costs. Repeat.
Keep him alive at all costs.
Well what do we do now Chief?
We are going to find Murphy,
get him to California,
and they are going to make a
vaccine and save the world.
And I'm gonna kill any bounty
hunter that gets in my way.
[wind blowing]
[blowing wind continues]
[growling]
[thud]
[growling continues]
[breathing heavily]
(Warren) Murphy!
차고야.
Garage.
[breathing heavily]
[gunshot]
[glass shattering]
[glass shattering] [tires squealing]
[crash]
[gunshot]
[breathing heavily]
[moaning]
[gunshot]
좋아 이거 정말이지 실제군
Okay. It's like that, then
[car engine running]
[gun cocking]
조심해!
Look out!
[gunshot]
조심해, 꼬맹아!
Look out, kid!
[gunshot]
[gunshot] [glass shattering]
10K! Murphy!
Ugh! 이거 뭔일이야?!
Ugh! What the hell is going on?!
이거 머피가 다들 풀어 논거야!
It's a damn Murphy free for all!
[gun cocking]
[growling]
내 생각에는 이제 슬슬
I think it's time we need to
가야 할때군!
Time to go!
[growling]
[tires squealing]
[explosion]
[electric guitar
theme music plays]
♪ Have mercy,
??Have mercy,
[gunshots]
♪ Oh, have mercy. ♪
??Oh, have mercy. ??/i>
- Sync and corrected by TheDelta -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[muffled gunfire and yelling]
아주 좋아,
All right,
헤어지자. Earl, 넌 나랑 같이 가.
we split up. Earl, you're with me.
남은 사람들, 뭘 해야 하는지 알지.
The rest of you, do what you got to do.
절대로 실수를 하지마.
But you make no mistake.
너희들 뭔 일 있음 알지 알아서 해
Any of you think you're gonna
go bag that buck yourself
그리고 사냥꾼들한테서 도망치고
and go running off with the bounty
날 믿어,
trust me,
그를 찾게 된다면 알지 우리가
갈꺼야.
cuz as sure as we can find him,
we will find you.
그리고 우리가 잡을꺼야
And we will cut you open
절대 굶지 말고.
and feed your insides to the dogs.
알았어?
You feel me?
절대 욕심 내지 말고 알아들어.
Just don't get all enterprising
is what I'm sayin'.
자, Murphy를 찾게 되다면 어떻게 할지 알지?
Now, what do we do when we find The Murphy?
[muffled gunfire and
yelling continue]
Wes?
우리가 그 놈 무릎을 박살낼꺼야.
We smash his knees till they break.
아니면?
Or?
발목이라도.
Or his feet.
좋아 쉬엄해.
All right, whatever's easier.
[laughing] 그녀석이 못 뛰도록
만들꺼야.
[laughing] Make for damn
sure he can't run no more.
[all laughing]
그러곤?
Then?
그 누구도 그를 못 알아보게 만들어야지.
We sack his head so nobody knows who he is.
그래 내말이.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
다른 질문은 없어?
What do we do to anyone else?
(all) 잡는거야.
(all) Put 'em down.
목적지까지 가는거야.
To the ground.
형제들이여 사냥 가자!
Brothers, let's go huntin'!
[muffled gunfire and
yelling continue]
[breathing heavily]
- [heavy breathing continues]
- [muffled gunfire and yelling continue]
- [growling]
- [fence rattling]
[muffled gunfire and
yelling continue]
[growling]
[gunshot]
[snarling]
젠장! 젠장! 집으로 가자!
Shoo! Shoo! Go home!
[growling]
[gunshot]
[thwap]
[muffled gunfire continues]
[snarling]
좀 가져다 줘.
Cut me some slack.
[splorch]
실례합니다, 아줌마?
Excuse me, ma'am?
궁금 한데요 같이 좀 갈 수 있을
까요...
I was wondering if I may be
able to catch a ride with y...
[gasping]
[growling]
[munching]
[thud]
[groaning]
오! 오! 병신 머저리!
Oww! Oww! Stupid jerk!
[rocket launching]
[loud explosion]
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[muffled gunfire]
[muffled gunfire continues]
[gunfire]
야 이 자식아 날 놀라게 했어.
You scared the hell out of me, kid.
난 어디에?
Where am I?
걱정하지마 우리가 챙겨줄께.
Don't worry. We got you now.
[gunfire]
뭐야?!
What?!
우리가 챙겨준다고! 너 말이 안들려!
I said we got you now! I can't hear you!
이런 미친!
Insane!
[gunfire]
왜 여기로 쏘는거야 도대체가
뭔 일이야?!
Why the hell is everybody
shooting at everybody?!
머피가 황금알을 품은 거위거든!
Cuz Murphy's the golden goose!
[gunfire continues]
오도 가도 못하네.
We're sitting ducks here.
소구모 그롭 대형으로 전환하구선
계속 가자고.
We're gonna have to split up
into groups and keep moving.
10K, 너 괜찮어?
10K, are you all right?
뭐?!
What?!
내 생각에 귀머거리야.
I think he's deaf.
[gunfire continues]
Doc. 너가 그를 좀 챙겨.
Doc. You take him with you.
너희가 골목으로 진입하고 동북쪽으로
펼쳐서 진형을 짜
You guys, get to the alley and
cut east and advance north.
Mack and Addy, 너흰 서쪽을 맡아.
Mack and Addy, you guys take the westside.
우리가 그를 포위하는거야
We'll flush him out.
그...그게 사냥꾼들은 어찌 해야 하나 ?
Well... well what about the bounty hunters?
그냥 죽여! [gun cocking]
Kill them too! [gun cocking]
내 신호에. 우리가 커버를 한다.
On my call. We'll cover you.
[gunfire continues]
Three, two, one.
Go!
[gunfire]
[screaming] Ahhh!
Addy!
[moaning]
너 맞았어?
Are you hit?
[moaning] 아니 난 괜찮어. 괜찮어.
[moaning] Yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
좋아 내가 커버 해줄께!
Okay. I got to get you movin'!
Okay! Okay!
좋아, 준비 된거지?
All right, ready?
[screaming]
준비?
Ready?
[gunfire]
[breathing heavily]
[muffled gunfire]
[gun cocking]
[snarling]
너희 정말 나를 힘들게.
You guys are killing me.
[snarling]
이쪽으로.
This way.
[snarling]
[breathing heavily]
너희 이걸 어떻게 무시를 할 수 있어
이게 뭔데?
You guys ever consider how
annoying this might be?
심각해.
이거 생각 할 수도 없네.
I mean seriously.
It's like a guy can't even think.
[snarling]
[breathing heavily] 아 정말 고마워.
[breathing heavily] I appreciate it. I do.
근데 여긴 내 구역이고,
저긴 너 구역인거야.
But this is my dance space,
and this is your dance space.
[snarling]
시간을 줘바.
A little me time.
내가 필요한거야.
That's all I'm asking.
[snarling]
Well
Hello, handsome.
[growling]
[gunfire]
[growling continues]
Murphy?
이거 원체.
It's got to be.
날 따라와.
Follow me.
Okay. Okay. 저 길로.
Okay. Okay. That way.
Okay.
[breathing heavily]
[yelling in Russian]
Go.
[yelling continues]
[muffled gunfire]
[muffled gunfire continues]
[speaking loudly] Murphy?!
[whispering] Shhh.
이게 내가 생각한거야. 준비 됐지? 가.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking. Ready? Go.
- [growling]
- [struggling]
[multiple gunshots]
- [groaning]
- [growling]
[screaming] Mack!
[growling]
[breathing heavily]
[gunshot]
가자.
Let's go.
[breathing heavily]
[man screaming in
distance] 가자고!
distance] Let's go!
[muffled gunfire]
[man screaming in
distance] 여기에 있다!
distance] Over here!
[muffled screaming and gunfire]
[growling]
[gunshot]
[growling] [grunting]
[growling]
[slam]
[taser clicking]
[growling]
[gunshot]
[thud]
[muffled gunfire]
[gunshot]
[gun cocking]
병신 같은 년
Damn bitch.
[gun cocking]
아냐 정말이지
Oh hell no.
[gunfire in distance]
Hey!
기다려 봐바.
Wait a minute.
내가 그를 잡았다!
I got him!
천천히 이 놈아!
Slow down, dude!
[breathing heavily]
Hey, 너!
Hey, yo!
내가 널 아프게 않아, 친구야!
I ain't gonna hurt ya, brother!
[snarling]
이거 좋아!
It's all good!
너 확실해, 친구?
You in there, bro?
Hey, 너희들!
Hey, yo guys!
여기에 그가 있어!
He's in here!
너와 나뿐인 것 같어, 친구.
I guess it's just you and me, bro.
(Doc) [muffled] 그가
이 빌딩에 있어.
(Doc) [muffled] He's
in this building.
(10K) [muffled] 이거?!
(10K) [muffled] This one?!
[muffled talking continues]
[muffled yelling]
우린 그를 여기로 데려와야 해.
The Zs must've followed him inside.
근데 내 생각엔 후퇴로를 알어.
좀 더 안전 할꺼야.
But I think I know a back entrance.
Might be safer.
너 내 말을 알아 들어?
Can you hear anything I'm saying?
[yelling] 뭐라고?!
[yelling] What?!
[gunshot]
오 주여!
Jesus!
이거 완전 미친 짓이야!
This is ridiculous!
우린 여기서 뭔일을 하는걸까?
What the hell are we doing here?
그게 과장 된 질문인 것 같어.
좋아 준비 된거야?
That's a rhetorical question.
All right, ready?
커버 해줄께. 넌 뛰어. One. Two. Three. Go.
I'll cover. You run. One. Two. Three. Go.
[gunshot]
젠장.
Damn.
[gun cocking]
누군가 우릴 꼼짝 못하게 하네.
Someone's got us pinned.
[gunshot]
[gun cocking]
Sniper.
좋군.
Great.
이층이야.
Second floor.
오른쪽 일곱번째 창문.
Seventh window from the right.
너가 그를 쓰러트릴 것 같아?
You think you can take him out?
[growling]
[gunshot]
[gun cocking]
- [glass breaking]
- [groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[mufflled gunfire]
[muffled gunfire and
yelling continue]
[whispering] 이거 선한 사람들을
위한 기회인건가
[whispering] Now is the
time for all good men
나라를 보호하는 사람들에게.
to come to the aid of their country.
[muffled screaming]
[click]
젠장할!
Damn it!
[groaning and grunting]
어디로 갈까?
Where are we going, man?
Come on!
너 이걸 원해?!
You want some of this?!
[crash]
[hit]
[groaning and grunting]
[gasping]
[breathing heavily]
[thinking] 이거 충분
한거가 그렇지
[thinking] Well that's
enough of that.
뭐야?
What the hell?
이게 다야?
Is this it?
마지막 발악이군.
The last rodeo.
방안 온도를 봐야하는데.
Time to assume room temperature.
Oh hey.
야. 이거 지붕 위에
있는 것 같아
Hey, there's a thing at
the top of the shelf.
Hey, man! 그냥 쏴!
Hey, man! Get that thing!
[gasping]
[thump]
[slice]
[gasping]
[breathing heavily]
[gurgling]
[crash]
뭐야, Doc?
What's up, Doc?
Murphy!
[breathing heavily]
What?
너 괜찮아?
Are you okay?
Murphy, 그가 여기에 있어.
Murphy, he's here.
그가 빌딩안에 있는거야?
He's in the building?
[gasping] 그녀석 가버렸는걸.
[gasping] He just took off.
[growling]
숨도 돌릴 틈 좀 줘?!
Give me a break, will ya?!
[growling]
Doc!
[gunshot]
[wind blowing]
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[whispering] 젠장.
[whispering] Shit.
[growling]
[gunshot]
[thud]
[growling]
[growling continues]
[gunshot]
[muffled gunfire]
[automatic gunfire]
이거 원 뭐가 불안 한데.
I'm afraid that ain't gonna be enough.
[laughs]
뒤 돌아.
I'd say turn back.
내 친구들이 금방 올꺼야
너 뒤에 있는 곳에서.
But my men'll be coming up
those stairs any second.
너가 있는 곳이 끝이야
여긴 막다른 골목인거야.
So any way you look at it,
you're in a tight spot.
[automatic gunfire]
[gunshot]
[laughing] 그건 아니야, 자기야!
[laughing] That ain't gonna do it, sugar!
[click]
Oh. [laughs] 얼마나 남았는데?
Oh. [laughs] How many left?
내가 기선제압을 한 것 같아!
Cuz I'm doing great over here!
[automatic gunfire]
[screams]
[groans]
이런…
Son of a
미친년!
bitch!
[groaning]
아 정말이지 아프네!
Yep, that stung. Oh!
내가 너한테 나쁜 짓을
I'm gonna have to do
할 것 같은데
bad things to you
널 죽이기 전에!
before I kill you!
[automatic gunfire]
[gunshot]
[hit]
[groans]
[whispering] 난 널
[whispering] I'm a
[whispering] 널 죽일꺼야.
[whispering] I'm a kill you.
[breathing heavily]
[laughing]
너 죽은 목슴이야, 난쟁아.
You're already dead, shorty.
[thwap]
[repeated hitting]
[coughing]
Thanks.
우리 나가야 해.
We got to go up.
난 떨어졌어.
I'm out.
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[gunshot]
[growling continues]
[screaming]
[echoes of water dripping]
[growling]
Move!
우리 뒤에!
Right behind us!
엎드려!
Get down!
[three gunshots]
우릴 따라와!
Follow us!
저기로.
Over there.
야 끝났어.
Hey. It's over.
웅 끝이야.
Yep. I'm done.
Hey, hey, hey.
그러지마, 너 뭐하는거야?
Don't. Don't What you doing?
진심으로 하지마.
I mean it. Don't.
Okay.
이런다고 뭐가 좋아?
What good is this gonna do?
Good?
이게 그렇게도? 결정적인거야?
What's it matter? What's the point?
야, 정말이지 우린 시간이 없어.
Come on, man. We don't have time for this.
I do.
난 시간이 많어.
I got all the time in the world.
Listen.
난 너 정신과 선생이 아냐.
우리가 여기 멀리 이렇게 하러 온건 아니야
I'm not your goddamn shrink.
We did not come this far for you
Oh my God. 너 정말이지 정신이 나갔어?
Oh my God. Do you even listen to yourself?
정말로 지겹지도 않어?
Doesn't that get old?
말해봐?
Saying that?
No.
[screaming] No!
[snarling]
엎드려!
Back down!
[snarling]
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[screaming] Addy!
[screaming] Mack!
Addy!
Go!
내가 널 구해 줄께!
I'm gonna get you out!
Go!
No!
[gunshot]
[whispering] 젠장.
[whispering] Shit.
Go!
[screaming] 제발 가!
[screaming] Just go!
[screaming] Warren을 찾아!
[screaming] Find Warren!
내가 널 구해줄께!
I'm gonna get you out!
[growling]
제발 가!
Just go!
No!
[grunting]
[growling]
[screaming] 제발!
[screaming] Please!
[screaming] Addy, 제발!
[screaming] Addy, please!
[screaming] 난 너가 내가 변하는 걸 못보여줘!
[screaming] I don't want you to see me turn!
[screaming]
[grunting]
No! No!
[screaming]
[growling]
[gunshot]
[snarling]
[growling]
[thump]
[snarling]
[growling]
[thump]
Come on!
[hit]
[splorch]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[snarling]
들어가!
Get in!
[glass shattering]
[thwap]
[smack]
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
[smack]
[growling]
(Murphy) 멈춰!
(Murphy) Stop!
멈춰!
Stop!
Addy! Hey! Hey! 충분해!
Addy! Hey! Hey! That's enough!
[screaming]
[groaning]
이게 뭐야?! 내가 그녀에게 뭔 짓을 한거야?!
What the hell?! What I ever do to her?!
너 괜찮어?
You okay?
[crying]
Mack은 어디에 있어?
Where's Mack?
[breathing heavily]
Mack은 어디에 있어?!
Where's Mack?!
[crying]
[breathing heavily]
서쪽으로 못 가겠군
Can't go west.
모래 폭풍이 앞길을 막네.
Dust storm is kicking up all that fallout.
이걸 뚫고 갈 길을 봐야해.
Gotta outrun that cloud.
[whispering] Yeah.
[whispers] 젠장.
[whispers] Damn.
- Sync and corrected by TheDelta -
- www.addic7ed.com -